Let's see how your load takes in an input image and detects multiple objects.
我们来看看 YOLO 如何接受输入图像并检测多个对象
Say we have a CNN that's been trained to recognize several classes,
假设有个 CNN 被训练成识别多个类别
including a traffic light,
包括交通信号灯
a car, a person, and a truck.
汽车 行人和卡车
We give it two types of anchor boxes,
我们为其提供两种类型的锚点框
a tall one and a wide one,
一个高的锚点框和一个宽的锚点框
so that it can handle overlapping objects of different shapes.
使其能够处理形状不同的重叠对象
Once the CNN has been trained,
CNN 被训练后
we can now detect objects in images by feeding at new test images.
我们可以向其提供新的测试图像并检测图像中的对象
The test image is first broken up into
测试图像首先被划分为网格
a grid and the network then produces output vectors,
然后网络生成输出向量
one for each grid cell.
每个网格单元对应一个向量
These vectors tell us if a cell has an object in it,
这些向量告诉我们某个单元中是否有对象
what class the object is,
对象的类别是什么
and the bounding boxes for the object.
以及对象的边界框是什么
Since we're using two anchor boxes,
因为我们使用两个锚点框
we'll get two predicted anchor boxes for each grid cell.
因此每个网格单元将有两个预测锚点框
Some, in fact most of the predicted anchor boxes will have a very low PC value.
某些（实际上是大部分）预测锚点框的 PC 值将很低
After producing these output vectors,
生成这些输出向量后
we use non-maximal suppression to get rid of unlikely bounding boxes.
我们使用非最大值抑制删除不太有用的边界框
For each class, non-maximal suppression gets rid of
对于每个类别 非最大值抑制都会删除
the bounding boxes that have a PC value lower than some given threshold.
PC 值低于某个给定阈值的边界框
It then selects the bounding boxes with the highest PC value,
然后选择 PC 值最高的边界框
and removes bounding boxes that are too similar to this.
并删除与该边界框非常相似的边界框
It will repeat this until all of
它将重复这一流程
the non-maximal bounding boxes had been removed for every class.
直到删除所有类别的非最大值抑制边界框
The end result will look like this,
最终结果将是这样的
we can see that yellow has effectively detected
可以看出 YOLO 有效地检测出
many objects in the image such as cars and people.
图像中的很多对象 例如汽车和行人
Now that you know how YOLO works,
你已经知道 YOLO 的工作原理
you can see why it's one of the most widely used object detection algorithms today.
可以看出它为何是现今使用最广泛的对象检测算法
Next, you'll get to work with the code implementation of the yellow algorithm,
接下来 你将学习 YOLO 算法的代码实现过程
and really see how it detects objects in
了解它如何从不同场景中检测对象
different scenes and with varying levels of confidence.
并具有不同的置信水平. 最新课程跟课件还有一对一辅导请加wx：udacity6